(Leonard:)It's not a big deal.
(Barry:)It's a huge deal.
(Barry:)Cooper, maybe physics
just isn't your thing.
(Barry:)Have you ever considered
a career in retail?
(Barry:)That way you could take
things back for a living.
(Leonard:)Okay, Barry, that's enough.
Oh, no, that's okay.
(Sheldon:)I can fight my own battles.
Isn't that right, "Bawwy"?
(Barry:)Is...?
Is that a reference
to my speech impediment?
That's pretty hurtful.
(Scene:)I...
I can't control it.
(Sheldon:)You're right,
(Sheldon:)that was uncalled for.
(Sheldon:)I take it back.
(Barry:)Of course you do.
Because you're the Retractor!
(Bernadette:)Raj, this dinner was amazing.
(Bernadette:)If you're here much longer,
I'm going to have
to buy bigger clothes.
(Sheldon:)Nonsense.
(Raj:)You need a little fattening up.
You've been locking
too skinny lately.
(Sheldon:)Aww.
(Bernadette:)Howie, how come you never
say anything sweet like that?